BRUNO SALA

Full Stack Web Developer brunosala.com

ABOUT

Hello! My name is Bruno Sala, I'm a Full Stack Developer based out of Chicago, IL. I've worked with a wide variety of clients from countries all over the world. My goal is to deliver high quality, bold products to my clients – all while having a bit of fun.

CONTACT

Email: connect@brunosala.com Phone: +1 (513) 668-7678 WhatsApp: +1 (513) 668-7678 Location: Greater Chicago Area

SKILLS - FRONT END

HTML5 CSS3, SCSS, LESS JavaScript, TypeScript Angular 2+, Angular Universal Bootstrap, Bulma.io, Skeleton

SKILLS - BACK END

NodeJS, ExpressJS API Development Apex, SOQL, Salesforce Automation PHP, mySQL, PostgreSQL MongoDB

EDUCATION

Moraine Valley - Palos Hills, IL Associate's Degree in Management and Information Systems

REFERENCES

Corey Simpson - COO International Legal Technology Association +1 (312) 533-4123 corey@iltanet.org

Phillip Bergner - CTO
All Digital Solutions
+1 (779) 800-9210
phil@alldigitalsolutions.com

CONNECT



LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/brunosala

Upwork - Top Rated goo.gl/kusu3B

EXPERIENCE

International Legal Technology Association

Front End Developer, Salesforce Developer | Oct 2018 - Apr 2020 | Chicago, IL

ILTA is a non-profit focused on promoting modern technology and security protocols to legal firms and government agencies.

- Responsible for the architecting of scalable components for collaborative development on websites, web applications, and mobile applications
- Driving the development and communication of new projects relating to ILTA's web presence
- ☐ Providing education to staff members on platform initiatives, modern tech standards, and CRM utilization
- Ensuring consistency with our various integrations between site CMS, membership CRM (Salesforce), and legacy content

Equiti Games | Start-Up

Front End Developer | Jun 2018 - Jan 2019 | Remote, California

Equiti Games is an Ethereum-based start-up aiming to provide a blockchain secured e-commerce environment focused on consumer digital media rights.

- Designed and developed the corporate and ICO websites for Equiti
- ☐ Provided marketing strategy in the form of email campaign automation, SEO, automated blog/site content, and social media management

BitBlog | Start-Up

Full Stack Developer | Jan 2018 - Sep 2018 | Remote, New York

BitBlog is a crypto-exchange start-up focused on cryptocurrency spending.

- ☐ Designed, developed, and scaled the ICO site with React and GatsbyJS
- Built e-commerce functions with blockchain APIs to enable Ethereum transactions

Elnsurance

Lead Full Stack Developer | Dec 2017 - Jun 2018 | Chicago, IL

Elnsurance is an affiliate lead generation site. Users enter their personal information and are matched with affiliate insurance companies.

- ☐ Lead a team of four to replace an 2000s ASP.net application with a PHP / Laravel back end. Migrated over 20,000+ users and 1,000+ affiliates
- ☐ Personally designed and refactored over 2,000+ pages and blog posts

Independent Contractor

Design, Development, Marketing, Strategy, Management | 2014 - Present

I've been freelancing my entire career - I handle client meetings, accounting, maintenance, security, and project work with efficiency and an acute attention to detail.